# CHARLESLEXCEL MENDOZA

**Q** Catalunan Grande, Davao City, 8000

+639062913082

itscharlesm@gmail.com



## **CAREER OVERVIEW**

Hard-working and self-motivated individual with excellent technological skills. An individual with much room for development in every aspect, an individual equipped with different basic skills through experience and perseverance, and lastly, a person with a good character.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Primary**

Saint Francis Xavier Learning Center

#### Senior High School

University of Immaculate Conception

#### College

BS Computer Science University of Mindanao

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

# COMMUNICATION

 Able to understand, read, and speak English language

# COMPUTER SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel
- · Slide presentations
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

# PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript
- Laravel Framework
- Java
- Python
- Flutter

#### PROGRAMMING PROJECTS

- Belens Beauty Parlor Management System | School Project | Vanilla PHP
- Annimunity | School Project | Flutter
- Hazard Payroll | DOST XI | Laravel Framework
- Enrollment System CQA Review Center | Laravel Framework

- Bookstore Management System | CQA Review Center | Laravel Framework
- Learning Management System | CQA Review Center | Laravel Framework
- Forms Management System | Advance Infinit Technology Solutions Incorporated | Laravel Framework
- Point of Sale System | Alexian Brothers | Laravel Framework
- Research and Publication System | University of Mindanao | Laravel Framework

### **EXPERIENCE**

- Service Crew Hitolicious Restaurant | January 2016 January 2017
- Freelance Encoder 8 Spatial | January 2021 March 2023
- Intern Web Programmer Department of Science and Technology Reginal Office no. XI | June 2023 - August 2023
- Chat Support INCOMATION | April 2023 October 2023
- Advisor Concentrix Corporation | October 2023 -February 2023
- Full-stack Web Developer Advanced Infinit Technology Solutions Incorporated | June 2024 -Present

# TRAININGS/ SEMINARS/ ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Code Your Future: 40 Mins Coding Workshop for Non-Coders in partnership with DICT Region XI and University of Mindanao | March 22, 2023
- Information Technology Specialist in Databases | Certiport — A PeasonVUE Business | June 13, 2023
- Information Technology Specialist in HTML and CSS | Certiport — A PeasonVUE Business | June 15, 2023
- Dean's Lister University of Mindanao | S.Y. 2020-2024
- Magna Cum Laude University of Mindanao | August 5, 2024